https://www.worldstamps.com/content/5-privacy-policy

> Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyWorldStamps.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.General Statement of PrinciplesAny information we gather through our web site is strictly for our use and is not shared with any other entity, public or private, for any reason - period. We will not sell or give away any lists or other data that we may retain and we do not purchase such information from other sources.Statistical DataOur servers (as most) track IP addresses and referring pages to help with site maintenance and improvements. This data is viewed only as anonymous statistics to show the busiest times of the day or week, pages with errors and how effective our advertising has been. This information is not used for any other purpose.Personal Information Collected - Order FormsWith the exception of credit card info, we store the information from your order form to allow us to track consulting issues or refer to a previous order to help provide some customer service. You may elect to have your information completely removed from this system by contacting us with your request. We do not store any type of sales information.Information Correction or RemovalIf you wish to correct, update or remove any information about you that may be in our records, you may do so by accessing your "My Account" page.  Alternatively, you can contact us with the details of your request. If you wish to contact us further, please find complete contact information on our contact page.Secure PaymentAll credit card transactions are 128 bit Secure Socket Layers (SSL) encrypted. The company registration documents and the site's registered domain name are checked and verified by a trusted certificate authority, ensuring the cardholder and merchant that nobody can impersonate WorldStamps.com to obtain confidential information.WorldStamps.com is committed to providing secure online services. All encryption complies with international standards. Encryption is used to protect the transmission of personal information when completing online transactions.WorldStamps.com internet servers are protected by firewalls and intrusion detection systems.WorldStamps.com does not have access to credit details.WorldStamps.com continually reviews and enhances its security in line with technological changes.
